United Airlines has apologised for mistakenly shipping an American family's pet dog
thousands of miles in the wrong direction to Japan.
The dog owner's beloved 10 -year -old dog named Buddy took an unexpected 16 -hour
flight to Tokyo following a mix -up by the airline.
The dog owner's family are currently in the process of moving.
They were meant to be reunited with the pet in their new home city in Texas.
But when they arrived at the United Airlines cargo facility in the southern U.S.
state, they found a stranger's dog waiting in Buddy's
But when they arrived at the United Airlines cargo facility in the southern U state,
they found a stranger's dog waiting in Buddy's place.
But when they arrived at the United Airlines cargo facility in the southern U.S.
state, they found a stranger's dog waiting in Buddy's place.
Both of the dogs had been sent to the wrong destinations on connecting flights from
Denver, with Buddy mistakenly being sent to Japan instead.
Buddy was given a fist